Fantastic Electro Game Music 20+ Tracks

THIS IS TRIAL DEMO VERSION.
Only 2 Tracks are included.

Best Electronic and Fantasy Game Music.

Beautiful and powerful synthesizer, Emotional melody. 
This perfectly fits for exciting scenes and movie trailers.
In this package you'll find 2 vocal tracks and 22 instrumental tracks.
All of the wav tracks are available as high quality 16 bit, and high quality re-mastered for using in games.
And, this pack includes ogg seamless loop with all music tracks.

*Here is purchase link
https://assetstore.unity.com/packages/slug/151882

If you like these music and want to add another one to your game,
Please get link and purchase. 

------------------

Trial Content

02. LAZZULI LUVS (Instrument)
12. New Gear




Produced by ISAo.

Website
http://airyluvs.com

E-mail
isao@airyluvs.com


*If you want to order new music or arrangement, please contact to me :)

Thanks.
2019/8/7
